LoganAlleyne

Web Developer

Contact







About.

I'm a Web developer based in Brighton & Hove who is strives to create visually appealing, meaningful, and clean web experiences using modern technologies.

I'm passionate about user experience and always try to pair aesthetic appeal & flare with functionality, usability, and accessibility.

Education

Computing for Digital Media (BSc hons) University of Sussex

A three year course including modules: Web 3D Applications, Human-Computer Interaction, Technology Enhanced Learning, and Software Engineering.

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma IT A two year A-level equivalent IT course

Skills_

Technology

HTML Vue GitHub
CSS & SCSS Vuex/Pina XML
TailwindCSS Nuxt REST APIs
JavaScript Node Vite
TypeScript Laravel Vitest

Experience

Technical Production Manager BrandStencil | Hove | Feburary 2021 - Present

Working on a charity focused templating & brand management SaaS. I am repsponsible for all template output, building the vast majority personally and overseeing the hire, management, and output of freelancersm& temporary team members when needed. Working with QA and Project Managers to ensure consistent high quality, pixel perfect yet dynamic templates with a very strong focus on UX and accessibility.

Software

Creative cloud

VS Code

Illustrator

InDesign Postman

Photoshop

In addition to this I am responsible for maintaining the front end of the application, designing & building any new features requested by stakeholders, and creating user focused improvements for the application.

Technology: HTML, SCSS, Tailwind. PHP, Laravel, Blade, JavaScript Vue, Vuex, REST APIs, XPath, XML, JSON, YAML, Docker, MySQL

Junior Product Developer ReedPop | Brighton | July 2020 - December 2020

Working a Junior Front-end web developer I maintained and updated an array of different sites, including Eurogamer.net and RockPaperShotgun.com. I also helped to build all new digital events sites for very large digital only events such as PAX x EGX for which we had over 12 million impressions.

Technology: Django, Python, Wordpress, PHP, Docker

Technical Operator The Edit_ | Brighton | September 2019 - July 2020

Working in television post-production, helping with assistant editing and technical support, with a broad number of responsibilities and a variety of challenges daily in a high pressure environment as part of a small highly collaborative team.

Technology: Avid Media Composer & NEXIS, PC Hardware, Networking